

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Details





in www.linkedin.com/in/yee-shim-chai-s10p1



NATIONALITY

Malaysian

Programming Skills

JAVA

Angular

Groovy

C-family Programming

HTML/CSS

Python

SQL

Visual Basic

Kotlin

Solidity

Soft Skills

- Fast Leaner
- Able to work under pressure
- Effective time management
- Collaboration & teamwork

Languages

Mandarin

English

Cantonese

Bahasa Malaysia

Profile

Experienced software engineer with a strong background in financial technology. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Possesses a skill set focused on Java and Angular development. Over the past two years, I have been responsible for customizing software and ensuring the delivery of high-quality products to clients. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Employment History

Software Engineer at Theta Service Partner Sdn Bhd

AUGUST 2022 — PRESENT

- Involved in CR development and supporting Hong Kong and India DBS & Charles Schwab Bank Loan Origination System.
- Developed REST APIs and integrated REST APIs.
- · Handled loan letters auto generation development.

Software Engineer Intern at Theta Service Partner Sdn Bhd

JANUARY 2022 — JUNE 2022

- Involved in R&D for the base product.
- Supported workflow-based Loan Origination System for multiple banks.
- Debugged software, identified root causes, and proposed solutions to software issues

Quality Assurance Analyst (Internship) at Finexus SDN. BHD., Kuala Lumpur

FEBRUARY 2020 — APRIL 2020

 Assured that system meet the established standards set by the company and free from errors.

Educational Background

Bachelor of Information Technology (Honours) in Software Systems Development, Tunku Abdul Rahman University of Management and Technology, Kuala Lumpur

JUNE 2020 — JULY 2022

Achievement:

- President's List (Jan 2021 & May 2020)
- Dean's List (Sep 2020)

CGPA: 3.91

Diploma in Science (Computer Science and Management Mathematics), Tunku Abdul Rahman University of Management and Technology, Kuala Lumpur

MAY 2018 — JUNE 2020

CGPA: 3.89

Projects

Garageku

Developed an e-commerce car workshop mobile application for a newly established company that act as an intermediary between car workshop owners and vehicle owners.